

# PAWEŁ OSTROMECKI

SENIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

I'm a Senior Fullstack Developer with over 7 year experience at rapidly growing companies. Worked on projects for Automotive, E-commerce, Manufacturing, Defence, Finance, Master Data Management, Registries. Business oriented, focused on developing efficient, user-friendly web and mobile apps. In brief ambitious, communicative and open-minded person.

## **FEATURES & SKILLS**

- Angular, React, Vue
- NX Monorepo, Module Federation
- RxJS
- Ionic, Capacitor, Android, iOS
- JavaScript, TypeScript,
- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- SSR (Universal, Nuxt, Analog, Astro)
- PWA
- NgRx, Vuex, Pinia
- Karma, Jest
- RWD, WCAG, ally
- Gitlab CI, Jenkins, Google Cloud Build, Azure Pipelines
- Node.js, Nest.js, Java, Spring Boot
- Agile, SAFE, Scrum
- Enalish C
- SQL, PostgreSQI
- Firebase, MongoDE
- Azure, Google Cloud
- Oauth, Auth0, Passport, Spring Security

#### CONTACT

Mobile.: (+48) 66l 546 446 E-mail: pawel.ostromecky@gmail.com Location: Wrocław, Poland Website: www.ostromecki.dev Github: https://github.com/ostromecky/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Senior Front-End Developer**

CSHARK (06.2024 - current)

- Developed and maintained drag drop form creator
- Worked on System Design, Improved Accessibility for production systems
- Improved Azure Pipelines for Front End Applications
- Stack: Angular 18, NX, Material CDK, Module Federation

## **Senior Front-End Engineer**

Stibo Systems (11.2023 - 05.2024)

- Developed functionalities for Stibo Systems Enhanced Content, PDX (Master Data Industry Product)
- Analysed and investigated architecture outlines and solutions
- Stack: Angular 16, NX, Node.js

## **Senior Front-End Developer (Freelancer)**

IT Bees (06.2023 - 10.2023)

- Developed functionalities for brand new mobile app Park Control 24
- Integrated native functionalities on Android, iOS (camera, notifications, network etc.)
- Stack: Ionic 7, Capacitor 5, Angular 16

#### **Front-End Developer**

GOD Nearshore (07.2021 - 10.2023)

- Developed and maintained enterprise ERP-class app for automotive industry
- Developed and maintained system consisted of 2 mobile apps created with Ionic. Old maintained in Ionic 3 + Cordova, new created from scratch with NX, Ionic 6, Capacitor 5

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Sendit S. A. (07.2020 - 07.2021)

- Developed and maintained web app for leading polish delivery broker
- Developed backoffice SPA
- Developed map web widget using Vue.js and vanilla JS
- Stack: Angular 12, SSR/PWA, Java Spring, Postgres, Gitlab Cl, Docker, SSR, PWA

#### **Front-End Developer**

Angry Nerds (01.2020 - 06.2020)

## **Junior Software Developer**

Exence S. A. (05.2018 - 12.2020)

#### **EDUCATION**

## Wrocławska Wyższa Szkoła Informatyki Stosowanej

BSE CS - Bachelor of Science in Engineering (Computer Science)